

Rok Jankovic

DATA SCIENTIST

Rok.jankovic14@gmail.com

Keyenveldstraat 55, 1050 Elsene, Belgium

+386-40-177-061

SUMMARY

A data scientist with more than 2 years of experience in the field of processing, analyzing, and visualizing data with working experience in R, Python, SQL and other technologies. During my professional career, I acquired solid experience in advanced modeling and database architecture. Moreover, I have basic experience in developing Web applications using Python/Django.

EDUCATION

2019-2021

MSc Quantitative Finance, WU Vienna, Vienna, Austria

2017-2018

(Erasmus Exchange) Finance, KU Leuven, Leuven, Belgium

2015-2019 BSc Economics, University of Ljubljana, Ljubljana, Slovenia

SKILLS-

Data analysis: Python, R, SAS, STATA Web applications: Django, Flask

Data bases: SQL

*Preparing for Google Cloud

Certification

LANGUAGES-

English: C2 Slovenian: C2

Croatian/Serbian: C2

German: B2 French: B1 Dutch: A2

EXPERIENCE

07/2021 – Present (3 months)

Leuven, Belgium

Data Scientist • Temporary contract • AB InBev SA/NV Data Scientist Intern • Internship • AB InBev SA/NV

03/2020 - 03/2021 (13 months)

Vienna, Austria

Risk Analyst • Student Job • Sberbank Eureope AG

03/2018 - 03/2019 (13months)

Ljubljana, Slovenia

Financial Analyst • Student Job • NLB Skladi d.o.o.

My main tasks were designing/conducting experiments, automating reports, and visulizing data.

PROJECTS

- OeNB University project Researching the predictive power of ML algorithms
- Data4Good Visualizing analized data from the refuge crisis - 2nd place - 2017

LEADERSHIP

Team Lead @ OeNB University project -Researching the predictive power of ML algorithms.

WEBSITE

To view some of my analytical projects visit: https://rokuc.github.io/